Guide to the Harris Masterson I papers,1860-1942, bulk 1880-1920 MS 468
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IX: Oversize materials (Boxes 279-282)
  - Memorandum of bills receivable for the Alamogorda Water Power Co. (2 pages)., 4-15-1910 to 7-23-1912 (Box 282, Item 37)
  - Bills payable (apparently for the Alamogorda Water Power Co., but not specified) from 2-8-1910 to 10-5-1915. (Box 282, Item 38)
  - State county taxes for 1906 in Harris Co. paid by H. Masterson. (Box 282, Item 39)
  - State county taxes for 1905 in Harris Co. paid by H. Masterson. (Box 282, Item 40)
  - State county taxes for 1904 in Harris Co. paid by H. Masterson. (Box 282, Item 41)
  - State county taxes for 1903 in Harris Co. paid by H. Masterson. (Box 282, Item 42)
  - Family tree of John Brown Sr., born 3-4-1768 in Swansea, MA. (Box 282, Item 43)
  - North end of Sec. 5 H.T. B. on Clear Creek (facts figures). (Box 282, Item 44)
  - Estate of T.W. DeWalt, in account with S.L. Gohlman. 2-1 through 4-9. (Box 282, Item 45)
  - Estate of T.W. DeWalt, in account with S.L. Gohlman., 9-28-1894 to 2-1-1895. (Box 282, Item 46)
  - Estate- Mrs. Lilly DeWalt, administratrix, Duke, TX, in account with S.L. Gohlman. Houston, TX, 11-13-1894. (Box 282, Item 47)
  - Estate- Mrs. Lilly DeWalt, administratrix, Duke, TX, in account with S.L. Gohlman. Houston, TX, 12-4-1894 to 1-24-1895. (Box 282, Item 48)
  - Estate- Mrs. Lilly DeWalt, administratrix, Duke, TX, in account with S.L. Gohlman. Houston, TX, 4-9-1895. (Box 282, Item 49)
  - Purchase record of 160 acres in Leon Co. by H. Masterson from L.E. Hibbard, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 50)
  - Purchase record of 320 acres in Harris Co. by H. Masterson from Jos. Megginson, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 51)
  - Purchase record of 863 acres in Harris Co. by H. Masterson from W.D.C. Hall, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 52)
  - Purchase record of 50 acres in Harris Co. by H. Masterson from Geo. B. McKeustry, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 53)
  - Purchase record of 640 acres in Harris Co. by H. Masterson from Hubbard Ralph, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 54)
  - Purchase record from (blank). (Box 282, Item 55)
  - In the matter of Jared E. Groce, bankrupt, copy of schedule B1 B5 and oath to schedule (part of petition)., 8-23-1892. (Box 282, Item 56)
  - Insurance policy for W.B. Fordtran by Houston, Harris Co.,TX (Houston Live Stock Insurance Co.)., 6-12-1908 (Box 282, Item 57)
  - Insurance policy for W.B. Fordtran by Houston, Harris Co.,TX (Houston Live Stock Insurance Co.)., 6-12-1908 (Box 282, Item 58)
  - Insurance policy for W .B. Fordtran of $2500 for 10 years (until 8-22-1921) (National Life Insurance Co.) 2 copies (Box 282, Item 59)
  - Purchase record of 294 acres in Harris Co. by H. Masterson from Jno. D. Taylor, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 60)
  - Purchase record of 640 acres in Harris Co. by H. Masterson from Manuel Tejerino, original grantee. (Box 282, Item 61)
  - Arabic document. (Box 282, Item 62)
  - Trial balance of the Landslide Oil Co. and report as of 4-16-1906 (W.T. Campbell, Sec. Tres) (2 pages-letter, 3 pages-facts figures). (Box 282, Item 63)
  - Bill of sale by Anson Jones to Samuel Lyons. (fragile on blue paper)., Oct. 11, 1858 (Box 282, Item 64)
  - Quit-claim deed- dated Oct. 15, 1874 for Edwin Estes. (Box 282, Item 65)
  - Record of sales list dated Dec. 21, 1878-Nov. 20, 1886 (8 pages). (Box 282, Item 66)
  - A.G. Reynolds League. Brazoria Co., TX (ca. June 18, 1887). (Box 282, Item 67)
  - Mercantile building forms dated Sept. 4, 1895 (Hartford Fire Insurance). (Box 282, Item 68)
  - Permit for Gasoline Stoves dated Sept. 1895 (Harford Fire Insurance). (Box 282, Item 69)
  - Statement from Texas Louisiana Lumber Co. (#4). Mr. Billy Bandwirpes (ca. Dec. 17. 1905). (Box 282, Item 70)
  - Texas Louisiana Lumber Co. sold to Billy Bandwirpes. Dated Dec. 17, 1905. (Box 282, Item 71)
  - Tax receipt for city of Houston for N. Masterson., 12-26-1906. (Box 282, Item 72)
  - Inventory appraisement for H. Masterson. Dated, Jan. 1, 1908. (Box 282, Item 73)
  - (2) Inventories of appraisement of property owned by W.A. Smith. Dated, Jan. 1, 1912. (Box 282, Item 74)
  - Land grant #353 vol. 12 for L.M. Openheimer. Dated, April 25, 1923. (Box 282, Item 75)
  - (2) pages of list of land owned by Powell Bros. and Sanders (description, number of acres, estimate of lands). (Box 282, Item 76)
  - Lands(?) to H.M. by So. Tex. Company. 10 pages 2 fragmented pages. (Box 282, Item 77)
  - Form for individual income tax return for 1917. (Box 282, Item 78)
  - Account with A.R. Masterson in [A.C.] with J.S. Mitchell & son. Brazoria, TX. (4 pages)., 9-29-1899. (Box 282, Item 79)
  - Bill of sale of land by Margarite Buye to Clark Beash. (2 copies)., 11-18-1838 (Box 282, Item 80)
  - Letter from Elliot Cage to W.P. Phillips., 8-10-1917 (Box 282, Item 81)